<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.7">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-09-06T23:52:09+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">The Dark Red Tower</title><subtitle>Tech-Blog by Jaime Bermejo</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Welcome to The Dark Red Tower</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/Hello-World/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to The Dark Red Tower" /><published>2020-07-10T00:00:00+02:00</published><updated>2020-07-10T00:00:00+02:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/Hello-World</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/Hello-World/">&lt;p&gt;Welcome to The Dark Red Tower, a place where share information, opinions, code and more about a lot of technology topics. In this blog you con find two main cornets; one of them dedicated to my own projects, and the other one dedicated to my code shown also in GitHub.
If you want to know more about me and who I am, you can click in “About” to read some information about me. 
You can find information in spanish and in english here.
Enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/Th3RedTower.png&quot; alt=&quot;_config.yml&quot; style=&quot;     display: block;     margin-right: auto;     margin-left: auto;     margin-bottom: 20px;     width: 80%; &quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bienvenid@s a The Dark Red Tower, un lugar donde compartir información, opiniones, código y mucho más sobre temas tecnológicos. En este blog podrás encontrar dos principales rincones, uno de ellos dedicado a mis propios proyectos (projects), y el otro dedicado a mi código (code) publicado también en GitHub. 
Si quieres saber más sobre mí y quien soy, puedes hacer click en “About” para leer alguna información adicional.
Podrás encontrar información en español y en inglés aqui.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;¡Disfruta!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Welcome to The Dark Red Tower, a place where share information, opinions, code and more about a lot of technology topics. In this blog you con find two main cornets; one of them dedicated to my own projects, and the other one dedicated to my code shown also in GitHub. If you want to know more about me and who I am, you can click in “About” to read some information about me. You can find information in spanish and in english here. Enjoy!</summary></entry></feed>